[
    {
        "question": "What is JS?",
        "optionA": "A script",
        "optionB": "a programming language",
        "optionC": "coffee",
        "optionD": "food",
        "answer": "B"
    },

    {
        "question": "Full meaning of DOM",
        "optionA": "Document Object Model",
        "optionB": "Director Of Management",
        "optionC": "Direct Object Management",
        "optionD": "Document Oriented Model",
        "answer": "A"
    },

    {
        "question": "What does document.getElementById do?",
        "optionA": "Gets all html elements",
        "optionB": "starts the web app",
        "optionC": "ends the web app",
        "optionD": "gets the element with the specified id",
        "answer": "D"
    },
    
    {
        "question": "Full meaning of CSS",
        "optionA": "Correct Style Sheets",
        "optionB": "Cursive Style Sheets",
        "optionC": "Cascading Style sheets",
        "optionD": "Code Sheet Styles",
        "answer": "C"
    },
    
    {
        "question": "Prevents a form from submitting until an action has been taken",
        "optionA": "e.preventSubmit();",
        "optionB": "e.preventDefault();",
        "optionC": "e.preventForm()",
        "optionD": "e.preventAction()",
        "answer": "B"
    },

    {
        "question": "Stores a value into local storage",
        "optionA": "localStorage.setValue();",
        "optionB": "localStorage.save();",
        "optionC": "localStorage.setItem()",
        "optionD": "localStorage.storeValue()",
        "answer": "C"
    },

     {
        "question": "Converts a json string into an object",
        "optionA": "JSON.parse();",
        "optionB": "JSON.convert();",
        "optionC": "JSON.object()",
        "optionD": "JSON.stringify()",
        "answer": "A"
    },

     {
        "question": "tag is an extension to HTML that can enclose any number of JavaScript statements.",
        "optionA": "SCRIPT",
        "optionB": " BODY",
        "optionC": " HEAD",
        "optionD": "TITLE",
        "answer": "A"
    },

     {
        "question": " What is the correct JavaScript syntax to write Hello World?",
        "optionA": "System.out.println('Hello World');",
        "optionB": " println('Hello World');",
        "optionC": " document.write('Hello World');",
        "optionD": "response.write('Hello World')",
        "answer": "C"
    },

     {
        "question": "The _______ method of an Array object adds and/or removes elements from an array.",
        "optionA": "Reverse",
        "optionB": "Shift",
        "optionC": " Splice",
        "optionD": "Slice",
        "answer": "C"
    }


]